<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>My life on Noé Gracia - Portfolio</title><link>https://noegracia.github.io/posts/my-life/</link><description>Recent content in My life on Noé Gracia - Portfolio</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2025 11:18:46 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://noegracia.github.io/posts/my-life/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>My first Marathon</title><link>https://noegracia.github.io/posts/my-life/sport/marathon-toulouse/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2025 11:18:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://noegracia.github.io/posts/my-life/sport/marathon-toulouse/</guid><description>&lt;h1 id="my-first-marathon-toulouse-2024">My First Marathon: Toulouse 2024&lt;/h1>
&lt;p>The adventure of my &lt;strong>first marathon&lt;/strong> started long before the actual race. From sweating through summer training to some calf pain and recovery rides on the bike, every step added up to that day. Here’s the story of my &lt;strong>42.195 kilometers around Toulouse&lt;/strong> and the experience of pushing my limits until my body had nothing left to give.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="training---the-long-road-to-42k">Training - The Long Road to 42K&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>It all started in &lt;strong>July 2024&lt;/strong>, when I began training for my first ever marathon. Most of my runs were &lt;strong>outdoors&lt;/strong>, exploring the city and nearby trails, gradually building up my endurance and pace. I trained mainly with a colleague, who not only shared the long runs but also motivated me to stay consistent — honestly, without him, I probably wouldn’t even have signed up for the marathon in the first place.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Aneto</title><link>https://noegracia.github.io/posts/my-life/mountain/aneto/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 16:18:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://noegracia.github.io/posts/my-life/mountain/aneto/</guid><description>&lt;h1 id="ascending-aneto-conquering-the-pyreneess-pinnacle">Ascending Aneto: Conquering the Pyrenees&amp;rsquo;s Pinnacle&lt;/h1>
&lt;p>The adventure began with anticipation as we gathered our gear, crampons and ice axes, essential for the challenge ahead. From the starting elevation of 1700 meters, we embarked on our ascent to 2140 meters, finding sanctuary at the Renclusa Refuge. Dinner was our prelude to rest, yet sleep proved elusive. At 9 PM, I nestled into my bunk, but the altitude, the cold, and a symphony of nocturnal noises (someone snoring) allowed for only two hours of light slumber.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>My routine</title><link>https://noegracia.github.io/posts/my-life/about-me/my-routine/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 16:18:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://noegracia.github.io/posts/my-life/about-me/my-routine/</guid><description>&lt;h1 id="my-daily-routine">My Daily Routine&lt;/h1>
&lt;h2 id="sports-and-physical-activities">Sports and Physical Activities&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Every day, I make sure to prioritize my physical well-being. My routine includes approximately 30 minutes of biking, which can vary depending on whether I&amp;rsquo;m working remotely or other factors. According to the World Health Organisation adults aged between 18-64 years should do at least 150–300 minutes of moderate-intensity aerobic physical activity, so I always like to do some cardio, moreover it makes me feel good. Apart from cardio I also like to do muscle strengthening. I usually do push pull legs workouts twice a week, whether it&amp;rsquo;s at the gym or at street workout parks. However, I also like doing diverse physical activities so I usually skip my workout days to do sports like tennis, volleyball, football, and even dance. My workouts are enough intense to progress but not too intense to be able to stick to my routine without being fatigued.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>My setup</title><link>https://noegracia.github.io/posts/my-life/about-me/my-setup/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 16:18:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://noegracia.github.io/posts/my-life/about-me/my-setup/</guid><description>&lt;h1 id="setup">Setup&lt;/h1>
&lt;p>My coding setup consists of a dual-monitor arrangement and a high-performance PC featuring a GeForce 3080, an i7-12700KF, 64GB RAM 3200MHz, and a 2TB SSD. This configuration allows me to efficiently handle large datasets and run resource-intensive algorithms, enhancing my productivity.&lt;/p>
&lt;img src="https://noegracia.github.io/posts/my-life/about-me/my-setup/my-setup.jpg" align="center" title="" width="400">
&lt;div style="margin-top: rem;">&lt;/div></description></item></channel></rss>