<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Life on Noé GRACIA</title><link>https://noegracia.github.io/categories/life/</link><description>Recent content in Life on Noé GRACIA</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 16:18:46 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://noegracia.github.io/categories/life/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Aneto</title><link>https://noegracia.github.io/posts/my-life/mountain/aneto/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 16:18:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://noegracia.github.io/posts/my-life/mountain/aneto/</guid><description>Ascending Aneto: Conquering the Pyrenees&amp;rsquo;s Pinnacle The adventure began with anticipation as we gathered our gear, crampons and ice axes, essential for the challenge ahead. From the starting elevation of 1700 meters, we embarked on our ascent to 2140 meters, finding sanctuary at the Renclusa Refuge. Dinner was our prelude to rest, yet sleep proved elusive. At 9 PM, I nestled into my bunk, but the altitude, the cold, and a symphony of nocturnal noises (someone snoring) allowed for only two hours of light slumber.</description></item><item><title>My routine</title><link>https://noegracia.github.io/posts/my-life/about-me/my-routine/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 16:18:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://noegracia.github.io/posts/my-life/about-me/my-routine/</guid><description>My Daily Routine Sports and Physical Activities Every day, I make sure to prioritize my physical well-being. My routine includes approximately 30 minutes of biking, which can vary depending on whether I&amp;rsquo;m working remotely or other factors. According to the World Health Organisation adults aged between 18-64 years should do at least 150–300 minutes of moderate-intensity aerobic physical activity, so I always like to do some cardio, moreover it makes me feel good.</description></item><item><title>My setup</title><link>https://noegracia.github.io/posts/my-life/about-me/my-setup/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 16:18:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://noegracia.github.io/posts/my-life/about-me/my-setup/</guid><description>Setup My coding setup consists of a dual-monitor arrangement and a high-performance PC featuring a GeForce 3080, an i7-12700KF, 32GB RAM 2400MHz, and a 2TB SSD. This configuration allows me to efficiently handle large datasets and run resource-intensive algorithms, enhancing my productivity.</description></item></channel></rss>